Guide to the Hisham Khatib Collection of photographic prints AD.MC.030
Akkasah: Photography Archive (NYU Abu Dhabi)
- Palestine and Trans-Jordan - Frank Mason Good, Bonfils, American Colony, J.Bendov et al (Object AD_MC_030_ref150)
  - 303 - Through the Rocks Jaffa. Celfen vor Jaffa. A travers la Passe. 21.3 x 27.8 cm, Circa 1898-1914; American Colony, Jerusalem (Object AD_MC_030_ref59)
    Albumen Prints; Boats/Ships; Coast; English Writing; French Writing; German Writing; Jaffa; Mediterranean Sea; Men; Palestine; Photographic Prints; Seas; Landscapes
  - 318 - Citadel of Zion. Zitadelle. Citadelle de Sion (Tower of David/Jerusalem Citadel) 21.3 x 27.8 cm, Circa 1898-1914; American Colony, Jerusalem (Object AD_MC_030_ref60)
    Albumen Prints; Animals; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Architecture; Carriages/Coaches; Horses; Jerusalem; Mount Zion/Jabal Sahyoun, Jerusalem; Palestine; Photographic Prints; Tower of David/Burj Dāwūd (Jerusalem Citadel); Forts/Castles
  - 321 - Jaffa Gate. Jaffa Thor. Porte de Jaffa. 27.5 x 21.2 cm, Circa 1898-1914; American Colony, Jerusalem (Object AD_MC_030_ref61)
    Albumen Prints; Animals; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Architecture; Buildings; Carriages/Coaches; English Writing; French Writing; German Writing; Horses; Jerusalem; Palestine; Photographic Prints; Clocks/Watches
  - 391 - Damascus Gate. Damascus thor. Porte de Damas. 21.3 x 27.8 cm, Circa 1898-1914; American Colony, Jerusalem (Object AD_MC_030_ref62)
    Albumen Prints; Animals; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Architecture; Damascus Gate, Jerusalem; Donkeys; English Writing; French Writing; German Writing; Jerusalem; Men; Palestine; Photographic Prints
  - 373 - Mosque of Omar. Omar Moschee. Mosquee d'Omar. 21.1 x 27.7 cm, Circa 1898-1914; American Colony, Jerusalem (Object AD_MC_030_ref63)
    Albumen Prints; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Architecture; Dome of the Rock/Qubbat al-Sakhrah; English Writing; French Writing; German Writing; Jerusalem; Mosques; Palestine; Photographic Prints; Religious Sites; Temple Mount/al-Ḥaram al-Šarīf
  - 377 - The Rock Moriah. Omar Moschee, der Celsen. La Roche dans La Mosquee d'Omar. 21.4 x 27.6 cm, Circa 1898-1914; American Colony, Jerusalem (Object AD_MC_030_ref64)
    Albumen Prints; Dome of the Rock/Qubbat al-Sakhrah; English Writing; French Writing; German Writing; Jerusalem; Mosques; Palestine; Photographic Prints; Religious Sites; Temple Mount/al-Ḥaram al-Šarīf
  - 380 - Mosque El-Aksa. Aksa Moschee. Mosquee d'El-Akca. 21.3 x 27.5 cm, Circa 1898-1914; American Colony, Jerusalem (Object AD_MC_030_ref65)
    Al-Aqsa Mosque/al-Masjid al-ʾAqṣā; Albumen Prints; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Architecture; English Writing; French Writing; German Writing; Jerusalem; Palestine; Photographic Prints; Religious Sites; Temple Mount/al-Ḥaram al-Šarīf; Mosques
  - 384 - Solomon's Stables. Salomonische Staelle. Ecuries de Salomon. 21.4 x 27.7 cm, Circa 1898-1914; American Colony, Jerusalem (Object AD_MC_030_ref66)
    Albumen Prints; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Architecture; English Writing; French Writing; German Writing; Jerusalem; Palestine; Photographic Prints; Temple Mount/al-Ḥaram al-Šarīf
  - 372 - General View of Temple Area. Gesamtansicht des Temples. Vue de la Mosquee. 21.2 x 27.5 cm, Circa 1898-1914; American Colony, Jerusalem (Object AD_MC_030_ref67)
    Al-Aqsa Mosque/al-Masjid al-ʾAqṣā; Albumen Prints; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Architecture; Dome of the Rock/Qubbat al-Sakhrah; English Writing; French Writing; German Writing; Jerusalem; Mosques; Palestine; Photographic Prints; Religious Sites; Temple Mount/al-Ḥaram al-Šarīf
  - 388 - Jews' Wailing Place. Klagemauer. Le Mur de Pleurs. 21.2 x 27.5 cm, Circa 1898-1914; American Colony, Jerusalem (Object AD_MC_030_ref68)
    Albumen Prints; English Writing; French Writing; German Writing; Head Covers/Veils; Jerusalem; Men; Palestine; Photographic Prints; Religious Sites; Temple Mount/al-Ḥaram al-Šarīf; Western Wall; Western Wall; Women; Group Portraits; Canes/Walking Sticks; Facial Hair
  - 745 - Jerash, Triumphal Arch. Dscherasch Siegesbogen. Djerach L'Arc Triomphe. 21.4 x 28.5 cm, Circa 1898-1914; American Colony, Jerusalem (Object AD_MC_030_ref69)
    Albumen Prints; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Architecture; English Writing; French Writing; German Writing; Jerash, Jordan; Jordan; Photographic Prints
  - 389 - Family Group (Jericho). Famille Indigeue A Jericho. 28 x 21.3 cm, Circa 1898-1914; American Colony, Jerusalem (Object AD_MC_030_ref70)
    Albumen Prints; Children; English Writing; French Writing; Jericho; Palestine; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; West Bank; Women; Buildings; Group Portraits
  - 747 - Jerash, Temple of the Sun. Dscherasch Sonnen-Tempel. Djerach Temple du Soleil. 23.3 x 29.2 cm, Circa 1898-1914; American Colony, Jerusalem (Object AD_MC_030_ref71)
    Albumen Prints; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Architecture; English Writing; French Writing; German Writing; Jerash, Jordan; Jordan; Photographic Prints; Religious Sites
  - 719 - Petra, Altar for Sacrificing. Altar der Aufopferung. Antel des Sacrifices, vu de pres. 23.3 x 29.2 cm, Circa 1898-1914; American Colony, Jerusalem (Object AD_MC_030_ref72)
    Albumen Prints; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; English Writing; French Writing; German Writing; Jordan; Landscapes; Mountains/Hills; Petra, Jordan; Photographic Prints; Religious Sites
  - 716 - General view of Mountains of Petra. Petra Gebirge. Montagnes de Petra, Vue Generale. 23.3 x 29.2 cm, Circa 1898-1914; American Colony, Jerusalem (Object AD_MC_030_ref73)
    Albumen Prints; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; English Writing; French Writing; German Writing; Jordan; Landscapes; Men; Mountains/Hills; Petra, Jordan; Photographic Prints
  - 713 - Trans-Jordan. Petra. Bab-es-Sik (Doorway to the Sik). Entrance to the gorge. 23.4 x 29.4 cm, Circa 1898-1914; American Colony, Jerusalem (Object AD_MC_030_ref74)
    Albumen Prints; Animals; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; English Writing; Horses; Jordan; Landscapes; Men; Mountains/Hills; Petra, Jordan; Photographic Prints
  - 1152 - Ramleh Vue Generale (Ramla general view). 20.9 x 27.7 cm, Circa 1870 - 1890; Zangaki Brothers (Object AD_MC_030_ref75)
    Al-Umri Mosque; Albumen Prints; Architecture; Buildings; French Writing; Men; Palestine; Photographic Prints; Ramla/ar-Ramlah; Facial Hair; Group Portraits; Landscapes
  - 244 - Damas (Damascus). 21.8 x 27 cm, Circa 1867-1880; Bonfils, Felix (Object AD_MC_030_ref76)
    Albumen Prints; Architecture; Buildings; Cemeteries; Damascus, Syria; French Writing; Landscapes; Photographic Prints; Syria
  - Jordan, near to Jericho. 24.9 x 30.3 cm, Unknown (Object AD_MC_030_ref78)
    Albumen Prints; English Writing; Jericho; Jordan; Jordan River; Landscapes; Palestine; Photographic Prints
  - 958 - Le Mont Carmel et la mer. - View of mount Carmel and the sea. (Elijah's sacrifice 1st Kings 18-19-40). 24.9 x 30.3 cm, Circa 1867-1880; Bonfils, Felix (Object AD_MC_030_ref79)
    Albumen Prints; Haifa; Landscapes; Mediterranean Sea; Men; Mount Carmel /Al-Karmil; Mountains/Hills; Outdoors; Palestine; Photographic Prints
  - Collage of men and sheep against a landscape. 27.9 x 35.5 cm, Unknown (Object AD_MC_030_ref80)
    Albumen Prints; Animals; Group Portraits; Landscapes; Men; Photographic Prints; Sheep; Regional/National Dress; Palestine; Facial Hair; Mountains/Hills; Turbans
  - Al-Aqsa Mosque (Temple of the ?). 26 x 31.6 cm, Circa 1870-1890; Studio Dumas Photagraphe a Beyrout (Lebanon) (Object AD_MC_030_ref81)
    Al-Aqsa Mosque/al-Masjid al-ʾAqṣā; Albumen Prints; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Architecture; Fountains; Jerusalem; Mosques; Palestine; Photographic Prints; Religious Sites; Temple Mount/al-Ḥaram al-Šarīf
  - 755 - Jerusalem (Environs) Jericho. 25.5 x 31.9 cm, Circa 1870-1898; Luigi, Fiorillo (Object AD_MC_030_ref82)
    Albumen Prints; Countryside/Rural; English Writing; Jericho; Jerusalem; Landscapes; Palestine; Photographic Prints
  - Jerusalem, Street in the Old City. 41 x 29.5 cm, Circa 1907-1927; Jacob Bendov (Ya'acov Ben-Dov) (Object AD_MC_030_ref83)
    Albumen Prints; Architecture; Buildings; English Writing; Hebrew Writing; Jerusalem; Men; Palestine; Photographic Prints; Streets/Roads
  - Jerusalem, The Old Monuments in the Valley of Jhoshaphath. 29.5 x 41 cm, Circa 1907-1927; Jacob Bendov (Ya'acov Ben-Dov) (Object AD_MC_030_ref84)
    Albumen Prints; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; English Writing; Hand-colored Photographs/Hand-tinting; Hebrew Writing; Jerusalem; Kidron Valley; Monuments/Memorials; Palestine; Photographic Prints; Tomb of Absalom; Tomb of Benei Hezir; Tomb of Zechariah; Tombs/Mausoleums; Religious Sites
  - Jerusalem, the Mosque of Omar (Dome of the Rock). 41 x 29.5 cm, Circa 1907-1927; Jacob Bendov (Ya'acov Ben-Dov) (Object AD_MC_030_ref85)
    Albumen Prints; Architecture; English Writing; Hebrew Writing; Jerusalem; Mosques; Palestine; Photographic Prints; Religious Sites; Temple Mount/al-Ḥaram al-Šarīf
  - Jerusalem, The Temple Place. 29.5 x 41 cm, Circa 1907-1927; Jacob Bendov (Ya'acov Ben-Dov) (Object AD_MC_030_ref86)
    Albumen Prints; Architecture; Buildings; Dome of the Rock/Qubbat al-Sakhrah; English Writing; Hebrew Writing; Jerusalem; Landscapes; Palestine; Photographic Prints; Religious Sites; Temple Mount/al-Ḥaram al-Šarīf; Mosques
  - Jerusalem, The Holy Rock in the Mosque of Omar (Dome of the Rock). 29.5 x 41 cm, Circa 1907-1927; Jacob Bendov (Ya'acov Ben-Dov) (Object AD_MC_030_ref87)
    Albumen Prints; Dome of the Rock/Qubbat al-Sakhrah; English Writing; Hebrew Writing; Jerusalem; Palestine; Photographic Prints; Religious Sites; Temple Mount/al-Ḥaram al-Šarīf; Tombs/Mausoleums; Mosques; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts
- Palestine, Lebanon, Syria and Cyprus - Bonfils, Circa 1867-1880 (Object AD_MC_030_ref151)
  - 1015 - Vue de Jaffa prise de la plage (view of Jaffa from the beach) and 1016 - Maison de Simon le corroyeur a Jaffa (House of Simon the tanner in Jaffa). 52.8 x 36.2 cm, Circa 1867-1880; Bonfils, Felix (Object AD_MC_030_ref88)
    Albumen Prints; Architecture; Beaches; Buildings; Donkeys; English Writing; French Writing; Houses; Jaffa; Men; Palestine; Photographic Prints; Regional/National Dress; Facial Hair; Group Portraits; Landscapes
  - 238 - Place de marche a Jaffa, vue generale (Market place in Jaffa) and 242 - Tour 40 martyrs, Rameleh. 52.8 x 36.2 cm, Circa 1867-1880; Bonfils, Felix (Object AD_MC_030_ref89)
    Albumen Prints; Animals; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Architecture; Camels; Donkeys; French Writing; Jaffa; Markets; Men; Mosques; Palestine; Photographic Prints; Ramla/ar-Ramlah; White Mosque, Ramla; Women; Religious Sites
  - 241 bis - Rameleh, vue generale prise de la tour (Ramla, general view from the tower) and Route de Jerusalem (Pass of Wady Ali in the Judean Hills). 52.8 x 36.2 cm, Circa 1867-1880; Bonfils, Felix (Object AD_MC_030_ref90)
    Albumen Prints; Architecture; Buildings; Cemeteries; Jerusalem; Landscapes; Men; Mosques; Palestine; Photographic Prints; Ramla/ar-Ramlah; Streets/Roads; White Mosque, Ramla; Religious Sites
  - Palestine, Village d'Abou - Goch, sur le route de Jaffa (Village of Abu Gosh) and 837 - Palestine - Kolonieh, vallee du térébinthe (Kuloniyeh, the valley of the terebinth). 52.8 x 36.2 cm, Circa 1867-1880; Bonfils, Felix (Object AD_MC_030_ref91)
    Abu Gosh; Albumen Prints; Architecture; Buildings; English Writing; French Writing; Jaffa; Landscapes; Palestine; Photographic Prints; Valley of Elah/Wadi es-Sunt
  - 244 - Port de Jaffa (Jaffa gate) and 251 - Tour de David, Jerusalem (Tower of David). 52.8 x 36.2 cm, Circa 1867-1880; Bonfils, Felix (Object AD_MC_030_ref92)
    Albumen Prints; Animals; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Architecture; Donkeys; Jerusalem; Men; Palestine; Photographic Prints; Tower of David/Burj Dāwūd (Jerusalem Citadel); Women
  - 277 - Reservoir d'Ezechias, Jerusalem (Hezekiah's Pool) and 848 - Jerusalem, Escalier allant au St. Sepulcre (stairs approaching the Holy Sepulchre). 52.8 x 36.2 cm, Circa 1867-1880; Bonfils, Felix (Object AD_MC_030_ref93)
    Albumen Prints; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Architecture; Buildings; Hats; Jerusalem; Men; Palestine; Photographic Prints; Reservoirs; Regional/National Dress; Turbans; Water; Women
  - 249 - Jerusalem, Saint Sepulcre, interieur (The interior of the Holy Sepulchre) and 246 - Facade du Saint-Sepulcre, Jerusalem., Circa 1867-1880; Bonfils, Felix (Object AD_MC_030_ref94)
    Albumen Prints; Architecture; Church of the Holy Sepulchre; Churches; English Writing; French Writing; Jerusalem; Palestine; Photographic Prints; Religious Sites
  - 853 - Cathedrale Greque dans la basilique du Saint Sepulcre (Greek Cathedral in the Basilica of the Holy Sepulchre) and 270 - XII et XIII stations le Calvaire, autel grec (the Calvary, Greek altar). 52.8 x 36.2 cm, Circa 1867-1880; Bonfils, Felix (Object AD_MC_030_ref95)
    Albumen Prints; Church of the Holy Sepulchre; Churches; English Writing; French Writing; Jerusalem; Palestine; Photographic Prints; Religious Sites; Statues/Sculptures
  - 266 - VII Station, porte judiciaire. - VII Station. The Judicial gate. (Via Dolorosa) and 252 - Arc de l'Ecce Homo, Jerusalem (Arch of the Ecce Homo). 52.8 x 36.2 cm, Circa 1867-1880; Bonfils, Felix (Object AD_MC_030_ref96)
    Albumen Prints; Architecture; Boys; Children; English Writing; French Writing; Group Portraits; Jerusalem; Lanterns/Lamps; Men; Palestine; Photographic Prints; Religious Sites
  - 257 - Jerusalem - tour Antonia (Antonia's Fortress) and 259 - Ruelle allant au palais d' Herode (Lane going to the palace of Herod). 52.8 x 36.2 cm, Circa 1867-1880; Bonfils, Felix (Object AD_MC_030_ref97)
    Albumen Prints; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Architecture; Boys; English Writing; French Writing; Jerusalem; Men; Palestine; Photographic Prints; Streets/Roads; Palaces; Children
  - 285 - Vue generale de l'emplacement du temple de Salomon (Haram es Sherif, the High Sanctuary) and 278 - Vue generale de la mosquee d' Omar (Kubbet es sakhra, the Dome of the Rock). 52.8 x 36.2 cm, Circa 1867-1880; Bonfils, Felix (Object AD_MC_030_ref98)
    Al-Aqsa Mosque/al-Masjid al-ʾAqṣā; Albumen Prints; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Architecture; Dome of the Rock/Qubbat al-Sakhrah; English Writing; French Writing; Jerusalem; Men; Palestine; Photographic Prints; Religious Sites; Temple Mount/al-Ḥaram al-Šarīf; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Mosques; Tombs/Mausoleums
  - 859 - Mosaiques, details exterieurs de la mosquee d'Omar - Mosaics: external details of the mosque of Omar and 279 - Interieur de la mosquee d'Omar, le rocher (The rock in the Kubbet el Sakhra). 52.8 x 36.2 cm, Circa 1867-1880; Bonfils, Felix (Object AD_MC_030_ref99)
    Albumen Prints; Architecture; Dome of the Rock/Qubbat al-Sakhrah; Jerusalem; Palestine; Photographic Prints; Religious Sites; Temple Mount/al-Ḥaram al-Šarīf; Tiles; Mosques; Tombs/Mausoleums; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts
  - 281 - Chaire de Cadi Borhan-ed-Din - The Pulpit of Cadi Borhan-ed-Din and 282 - Mosquee El Aksa - Al Aksa Mosque. 52.8 x 36.2 cm, Circa 1867-1880; Bonfils, Felix (Object AD_MC_030_ref100)
    Al-Aqsa Mosque/al-Masjid al-ʾAqṣā; Albumen Prints; Architecture; Dome of the Rock/Qubbat al-Sakhrah; English Writing; French Writing; Jerusalem; Mosques; Palestine; Photographic Prints; Religious Sites; Temple Mount/al-Ḥaram al-Šarīf; Buildings
  - 863 - Jerusalem, Details interieurs de la mosquee El Aksa - Interior of Al-Aksa mosque and 276 - Porte Doree interieur, Jerusalem (The Golden Gate). 52.8 x 36.2 cm, Circa 1867-1880; Bonfils, Felix (Object AD_MC_030_ref101)
    Al-Aqsa Mosque/al-Masjid al-ʾAqṣā; Albumen Prints; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Architecture; English Writing; French Writing; Golden Gate, Jerusalem; Greek Writing; Jerusalem; Mosques; Palestine; Photographic Prints; Religious Sites; Buildings
  - 245 - Mur des Juifs un vendredi (The Jews' wailing place, a Friday) and 867 - Arche de Robinson, Jerusalem (Robinson's Arch). 52.8 x 36.2 cm, Circa 1867-1880; Bonfils, Felix (Object AD_MC_030_ref102)
    Albumen Prints; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Architecture; English Writing; French Writing; Jerusalem; Men; Palestine; Photographic Prints; Religious Sites; Temple Mount/al-Ḥaram al-Šarīf; Western Wall; Women; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Head Covers/Veils; Praying
  - 287 - Porte de Damas (The Damascus Gate) and 883 Grotte de Jeremie et couvent Saint-Etienne a Jerusalem (Cave of Jeremiah and St. Stephen's Convent in Jerusalem, El Heidemiyeh). 52.8 x 36.2 cm, Circa 1867-1880; Bonfils, Felix (Object AD_MC_030_ref103)
    Albumen Prints; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Architecture; Damascus Gate, Jerusalem; English Writing; French Writing; Men; Palestine; Photographic Prints; Religious Sites; Umbrellas/Parasols; Women
  - 321 - Tombeau des Rois cour interieurs, Jerusalem (Tomb of Helena of Adiabene, known as Tomb of the Kings) and 292 Mont des Oliviers, Jerusalem (Mount of Olives). 52.8 x 36.2 cm, Circa 1867-1880; Bonfils, Felix (Object AD_MC_030_ref104)
    Albumen Prints; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; English Writing; French Writing; Jerusalem; Mount of Olives/Jabal al-Zaytun, Jerusalem; Palestine; Photographic Prints; Tombs/Mausoleums; Religious Sites
  - *** missing two partial scans *** 302 bis - Jerusalem du Mont des Oliviers (Jerusalem from the mount of Olives)
  - *** missing three partial scans *** 300 - Panoramic view of Jerusalem from the mount of Olives
  - 295 - Coupole de l'assencion (Chapel of the Ascension) and 879 Mer morte prise du mont des Oliviers (The Dead Sea taken from the Mount of Olives). 52.8 x 36.2 cm, Circa 1867-1880; Bonfils, Felix (Object AD_MC_030_ref107)
    Albumen Prints; Architecture; Dead Sea; English Writing; French Writing; Jerusalem; Landscapes; Men; Mount of Olives/Jabal al-Zaytun, Jerusalem; Palestine; Photographic Prints; Religious Sites; Temples; Chapel of the Ascension
  - 305 - Olivier du Jardin de Gethsemanee, Jerusalem (Traditional Garden of Gethsemane) and 290 - Valee de Josaphat (Valley of Josaphat). 52.8 x 36.2 cm, Circa 1867-1880; Bonfils, Felix (Object AD_MC_030_ref108)
    Albumen Prints; English Writing; French Writing; Gethsemane, Jerusalem; Jerusalem; Landscapes; Men; Mount of Olives/Jabal al-Zaytun, Jerusalem; Palestine; Photographic Prints; Religious Sites
  - 310 - Valee de Josaphat (Valley of Josaphat, Kidron Valley, Tomb of Absolom, Tomb of Zacharias) and 329 - Vallee du Tiropeon (Tyropoeon Valley). 52.8 x 36.2 cm, Circa 1867-1880; Bonfils, Felix (Object AD_MC_030_ref109)
    Albumen Prints; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Architecture; Cemeteries; English Writing; French Writing; Jerusalem; Kidron Valley; Landscapes; Monuments/Memorials; Palestine; Photographic Prints; Temple Mount/al-Ḥaram al-Šarīf; Tomb of Absalom; Tomb of Zechariah; Tombs/Mausoleums; Religious Sites
  - 315 - Vue generale de Siloe (Siloam) and 316 - Piscine de Siloe (Pool of Siloam). 52.8 x 36.2 cm, Circa 1867-1880; Bonfils, Felix (Object AD_MC_030_ref110)
    Albumen Prints; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Architecture; Buildings; English Writing; French Writing; Jerusalem; Landscapes; Men; Palestine; Photographic Prints; Siloam/Silwan
  - 317 - Champ du sang au valée de Hinnom (The Field of Blood in the Valley of Hinnom) and 846 - Forteresse pres de la porte de Jaffa, Jerusalem (fortifications of Jerusalem, just south of the Jaffa Gate). 52.8 x 36.2 cm, Circa 1867-1880; Bonfils, Felix (Object AD_MC_030_ref111)
    Albumen Prints; Animals; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Architecture; Buildings; Carriages/Coaches; Donkeys; English Writing; Forts/Castles; French Writing; Gehenna/Valley of Hinnom; Horses; Jaffa Gate, Jerusalem; Jerusalem; Landscapes; Men; Palestine; Photographic Prints; Religious Sites
  - 888 - Route de Bethlehem prise de la porte de Jaffa, Jerusalem (Road to Bethlehem and Hebron from the Jaffa Gate) and 1041 - Mont Sion et Mont des Oliviers de la route de Bethlehem (The north end of Mount Zion from the Bethlehem road). 52.8 x 36.2 cm, Circa 1867-1880 (Object AD_MC_030_ref112)
    Albumen Prints; Animals; Buildings; Donkeys; English Writing; Forts/Castles; French Writing; Goats; Jaffa Gate, Jerusalem; Jerusalem; Landscapes; Men; Mount of Olives/Jabal al-Zaytun, Jerusalem; Mount Zion/Jabal Sahyoun, Jerusalem; Palestine; Photographic Prints; Tents
  - 339 - Chene d'Abraham, Palestine ("Abraham's Oak" Oak of Mamre) and 338 - Vue generale d'Hebron (Hebron). 52.8 x 36.2 cm, Circa 1867-1880; Bonfils, Felix (Object AD_MC_030_ref113)
    Albumen Prints; Animals; Buildings; English Writing; French Writing; Horses; Landscapes; Mamre/Ramat el-Khalil; Men; Outdoors; Palestine; Photographic Prints
  - Enclosure wall of the Great Mosque, Hebron and View of the Mausoleum and Mosque of Abraham from the east. 52.8 x 36.2 cm, Circa 1867-1890; Unknown (Object AD_MC_030_ref114)
    Albumen Prints; Architecture; Cave of the Patriarchs/Cave of Machpelah/Al-Haram al-Ibrahimi; Men; Mosques; Palestine; Photographic Prints; Religious Sites; Sanctuary of Abraham/Ibrahimi Mosque; West Bank; Synagogues; Facial Hair; Individual Portraits
  - 337 - Vue generale vasques de Salomon (general view of Solomon's Pools) and 330 bis - Vue generale de Bethlehem (general view of Bethlehem). 52.8 x 36.2 cm, Circa 1867-1880; Bonfils, Felix (Object AD_MC_030_ref115)
    Al-Khader; Albumen Prints; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Architecture; Bethlehem; Buildings; English Writing; French Writing; Landscapes; Palestine; Photographic Prints; Reservoirs; Solomon's Pools/El-Burak; Water
  - 334 - Eglise de la Nativite, interieur (interior of the Church of the Nativity) and 893 Bethlehem grotte de la nativite, la creche (Grotto of the Nativity, the crib). 52.8 x 36.2 cm, Circa 1867-1880; Bonfils, Felix (Object AD_MC_030_ref116)
    Albumen Prints; Bethlehem; Church of the Nativity; Churches; English Writing; French Writing; Palestine; Photographic Prints; Religious Sites; West Bank
  - 623 - Femmes de Bethlehem allant a l'eau (Women of Bethlehem collecting water) and 895 - Champ de Boaz, aux environs de Bethlehem (Field of Boaz, near Bethlehem). 52.8 x 36.2 cm, Circa 1867-1880; Bonfils, Felix (Object AD_MC_030_ref117)
    Albumen Prints; Bethlehem; Children; English Writing; French Writing; Landscapes; Palestine; Photographic Prints; Religious Sites; Regional/National Dress; Water; Women
  - 899 - Couvent de Mar-Saba vue generale, les deux tours (Monastery of Mar Saba) and 341 - La Mer Morte, Palestine (The Dead Sea, north shore). 52.8 x 36.2 cm, Circa 1867-1880; Bonfils, Felix (Object AD_MC_030_ref118)
    Albumen Prints; Bethlehem; Dead Sea; English Writing; French Writing; Kidron Valley; Mar Saba/The Holy Lavra of Saint Sabbas the Sanctified; Monasteries/Convents; Palestine; Photographic Prints; Religious Sites; Seas; West Bank; Landscapes; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Mountains/Hills; Water; Buildings; Architecture; Monasteries/Convents
  - 917 - Courbe et cours du Jourdain (Curve and course of the River Jordan) and 915 - Halte des voyageurs sur le bords du Jourdain (Resting place of travelers on the shores of the Jordan). 52.8 x 36.2 cm, Circa 1867-1880; Bonfils, Felix (Object AD_MC_030_ref119)
    Albumen Prints; Bedouins; English Writing; Jordan; Jordan River; Landscapes; Men; Outdoors; Photographic Prints; Rivers; Facial Hair; Group Portraits; Water
  - *** missing one partial scan *** 753 - Campement de Bedouin a Jericho, Palestine, Circa 1867-1885; Bonfils, Felix
    Albumen Prints; Bedouins; Boys; English Writing; French Writing; Jericho; Landscapes; Men; Monastery of St. George of Choziba; Monasteries/Convents; Mount Quarantania/Jabal al-Qarantal, Jericho; Mountains/Hills; Palestine; Photographic Prints; Wadi Qelt/Wadi Kelt; West Bank; Women